Leslie Crow Papers
Holt-Atherton Department of Special Collections
- Series III: Research Files, 1850-2006
  - Box 18
    - Subseries: Stockton, 1850-2006 (cont.)
      - 18.18 Stockton Police Department
      - 18.19 Stockton Record Building
      - 18.20 Stockton Reprographic Survey
      - 18.21 Stockton Rural Cemetery
      - 18.22 Stockton Savings Bank
      - 18.23 Stockton Savings and Loan Building
      - 18.24 Stockton Savings and Loan Society
      - 18.25 Stockton Savings and Loan Society Founders
      - 18.26 Stockton Savings and Loan Society-Note on Site Selection
      - 18.27 Stockton Scams
      - 18.28 Stockton Sesquicentennial, 2000
      - 18.29 Stockton Special Neighborhoods Architectural Survey
      - 18.30 Stockton State Hospital
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans, Box 26) Stockton State Hospital-Doctors Residence Plans, 1940, 1976
      - 18.31 Stockton State Hospital-Superintendents Residence, Correspondence
      - 18.32 Stockton State Hospital-Superintendents Residence, Feasibility Study
      - 18.33 Stockton State Hospital-Superintendents Residence, History
      - 18.34 Stockton State Hospital-Superintendents Residence, Illustrations
      - 18.35 Stockton State Hospital-Superintendents Residence, Proposal
      - 18.36 Stockton State Hospital-Superintendents Residence, Research
      - 18.37 Stockton Street Names
      - 18.38 Stockton Street Railroads
      - 18.39 Stockton Surveys-Mapping
      - 18.40 Stockton Waterfront International Market
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Stockton Waterfront Redevelopment, 1997
      - 18.41 Stockton Waterfront Revival (1 of 3)
      - 18.42 Stockton Waterfront Revival (2 of 3)
      - 18.43 Stockton Waterfront Revival (3 of 3)
  - Box 19
    - Subseries: Stockton, 1850-2006 (cont.)
      - 19.1 Stockton Waterways-History
      - 19.2 Stockton Waterways-Illustrations
      - 19.3 Stockton Waterways-Research (1 of 2)
      - 19.4 Stockton Waterways-Research (2 of 2)
      - 19.5 Streetcar Barn
      - 19.6 Studebaker Garage / Gaia-Delucchi
      - 19.7 Sunset Telephone Company Building
      - 19.8 Swinton, Ernest, in Stockton
      - 19.9 T and D Theatre
      - 19.10 Telephone
      - 19.11 Temple Israel (1 of 3)
      - 19.12 Temple Israel (2 of 3)
      - 19.13 Temple Israel (3 of 3)
      - 19.14 Temple Israel Proposal
      - 19.15 Terry, Sarah Althea
      - 19.16 Theater History, Stockton
      - 19.17 Thornton
      - 19.18 Thrift, E. E.
      - 19.19 Tidewater Southern Railway
      - 19.20 Tinkham, George H., History
      - 19.21 Transit Center Block
      - 19.22 Tretheway Building
      - 19.23 Trinity Lutheran Church
      - 19.24 Turn Verein Hall
      - 19.25 Tuxedo Park
      - 19.26 Union Flour Mill
      - 19.27 Union Planing Mill
      - 19.28 Union Safe Deposit Bank
      - 19.29 United Brethren Church
      - 19.30 University of the Pacific-Architecture
      - 19.31 University of the Pacific-Fifty Years
      - 19.32 University of the Pacific-Seventieth Founders Day Campus Rededication, 1995
      - 19.33 University Park
      - 19.34 Vail, Frederic
      - 19.35 Venetian Court Apartments
      - 19.36 Viet Nam Memorial
      - 19.37 Virginia S.
      - 19.38 Walking Tour Brochure Notes
      - 19.39 Walking Tour Information
      - 19.40 Wallace, B. C.
      - 19.41 Walters, Benjamin
      - 19.42 Washington Monument
      - 19.43 Weber Avenue-History
      - 19.44 Weber Avenue / Mormon Slough-Consulting
      - 19.45 Weber Avenue / Mormon Slough-Report
      - 19.46 Weber Avenue / Mormon Slough-Research
      - 19.47 Weber Avenue-Railroad Rights-of-Way
      - 19.48 Weber Block
      - 19.49 Weber, Charles M.
      - 19.50 Weber Family Photos
      - 19.51 Weber, Helen Murphy
      - 19.52 Weber Homesite Monument
      - 19.53 Weber House Archaeology Report, 2000
  - Box 20
    - Subseries: Stockton, 1850-2006 (cont.)
      - 20.1 Weber, Julia
      - 20.2 Weber, Julia, Homesite
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Weber Point, 1997-2000
      - 20.3 Weber Point Events Center
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Weber Point Events Center Publicity
      - 20.4 Weber Point Images (1 of 3)
      - 20.5 Weber Point Images (2 of 3
      - 20.6 Weber Point Images (3 of 2)
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Weber Point Tent, 1999; Gold Fever! [1999]
      - 20.7 Weber, Thomas Jefferson
      - 20.8 Wells, James
      - 20.9 Welsh Residence
      - 20.10 West Family
      - 20.11 Western Pacific Railroad Depot
      - 20.12 Western Pacific Railroad Depot-Illustrations
      - 20.13 Western Pacific Railroad Depot-Nomination
      - 20.14 Whang Ho
      - 20.15 Wilde, Oscar
      - 20.16 Wilhoit, R. E.
      - 20.17 Wong Mansion
      - 20.18 Woodmen HallLafayette Street
      - 20.19 Woods, Rev. James
      - 20.20 Woolen Mill
      - 20.21 Womens History-Local
      - 20.22 Womens Suffrage-Stockton
      - 20.23 Wright, William James
      - 20.24 Yacht Club
      - 20.25 Yardley, Ralph
      - 20.26 YMCA Building
      - 20.27 Yore, Stanley / Gloria Ice Cream
      - 20.28 Yosemite Club
      - 20.29 Yosemite Hotel
      - 20.30 Yosemite Terrace
      - 20.31 Yosemite Theater
      - 20.32 Yosemite Valley Attack
      - 20.33 Young, Charles
      - 20.34 Ziegler, August
      - 20.35 Zinc House
      - 20.36 Various Properties-905 / 919 N. California Street
      - 20.37 Various Properties-850 E. Channel Street
      - 20.38 Various Properties-1045 N. Commerce, Joseph Swain
      - 20.39 Various Properties-347 N. El Dorado
      - 20.40 Various Properties-600 N. El Dorado
      - 20.41 Various Properties-705 N. El Dorado
      - 20.42 Various Properties-710 N. Grant Street
      - 20.43 Various Properties-Lafayette Street
      - 20.44 Various Properties-144 E. Lafayette / 315 S. Hunter
      - 20.45 Various Properties-230 E. Main Street
      - 20.46 Various Properties-343 E. Main Street
      - 20.47 Various Properties-500 E. Main Street
      - 20.48 Various Properties-122 E. Poplar (1 of 2)
      - 20.49 Various Properties-122 E. Poplar (2 of 2)
      - 20.50 Various Properties-144 E. Poplar
      - 20.51 Various Properties-428 E. Poplar
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans, Box 26) Various Properties-428 E. Poplar, Remodel Plans, 2000
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans, Box 26) Various Properties-640 N. San Joaquin Street, Fire Escape Plans, 2001
      - 20.52 Various Properties-1280 N. San Joaquin Street
      - 20.53 Various Properties-1633 N. San Joaquin Street
      - 20.54 Various Properties-47-41-39-35-33 S. San Joaquin Street, Built 1914
      - 20.55 Various Properties-921 S. San Joaquin Street
      - 20.56 Unsorted Newspaper Clippings
      - 20.57 Unsorted Notes
  - Box 21
    - Subseries: Stockton, 1850-2006 (cont.)
      - 21.1 Unsorted Notepads (1 of 4)
      - 21.2 Unsorted Notepads (2 of 4)
      - 21.3 Unsorted Notepads (3 of 4)
      - 21.4 Unsorted Notepads (4 of 4)
      - 21.5 Unsorted Photocopies (1 of 3)
      - 21.6 Unsorted Photocopies (2 of 3)
      - 21.7 Unsorted Photocopies (3 of 3)
      - 21.8 Photographs, Slides, and Images-Buildings (1 of 5)
      - 21.9 Photographs, Slides, and Images-Buildings (2 of 5)
      - 21.10 Photographs, Slides, and Images-Buildings (3 of 5)
      - 21.11 Photographs, Slides, and Images-Buildings (4 of 5)
      - 21.12 Photographs, Slides, and Images-Buildings (5 of 5)
      - 21.13 Photographs, Slides, and Images-People and Events (1 of 9)
      - 21.14 Photographs, Slides, and Images-People and Events (2 of 9)
      - 21.15 Photographs, Slides, and Images-People and Events (3 of 9)
      - 21.16 Photographs, Slides, and Images-People and Events (4 of 9)
      - 21.17 Photographs, Slides, and Images-People and Events (5 of 9)
      - 21.18 Photographs, Slides, and Images-People and Events (6 of 9)
      - (See Oversize, Box 24) Photographs, Slides, and Images-People and Events (7 of 9)
      - (See Oversize, Box 24) Photographs, Slides, and Images-People and Events (8 of 9)
      - 21.19 Photographs, Slides, and Images-People and Events (9 of 9)
  - Box 22
    - Subseries: Trinity County, 1979
      Includes historic resources inventory.
      - 22.1 Trinity County Survey
    - Subseries: Tuolumne County, 1981-2005
      Includes correspondence, historic resource inventories, photographs, address lists, maps, consulting proposal, applications for designation as officially recognized historic resources, handwritten and photocopied notes, newspaper clippings, and photocopied articles, and travel brochure.
      - 22.2 Correspondence
      - 22.3 Historic Resources Inventories
      - 22.4 Jamestown Site-ASI
      - 22.5 Tuolumne County
      - 22.6 Yosemite Junction Hotel
    - Subseries: Yosemite National Park, 1984
      Includes correspondence, announcements, notes, 35mm slides, trade mark lists, and photocopies.
      - 22.7 Yosemite History Center (1 of 2)
      - 22.8 Yosemite History Center (2 of 2)
- Series IV: VHS Cassettes, 1928-2001
  Includes videos of newscasts, council meetings, and historical documentaries.
  - Box 23
    - Cunningham Hotel (1998)
    - Downtown Stockton: Past, Present, and Future (2001)
    - Fox Theatre (1996)
    - Gold Fever! [1999]
    - Good Old Days Remembered [n.d.]
    - Ripon Enters the Movies (1928)
    - Stockton City Seal (1997)
    - Stockton Concealed Weapon Issue (1994)
    - Stockton Development Center (1997)
    - Stockton Downtown Development (1995?)
    - Stockton Downtown Promotion (1996)
    - Stockton Waterfront Redevelopment (1997)
    - Stockton Waterfront Taskforce [n.d.]
    - Weber Point (1998-2000)
    - Weber Point Tent (1999); Gold Fever! [1999]
- Series V: Oversize, 1950-2004
  Includes maps, posters, research material, plans, committee notes, and photographic images.
  - Box 24
    - 24.1 Copperopolis Maps
    - 24.2 Fox California Theatre-Publicity
    - 24.3 Linden Irrigation District
    - 24.4 Lockeford School Plans
    - 24.5 Maps of Stockton, 1850-1923
    - 24.6 Photocopied Photographs from the Haggin Museum
    - 24.7 Photographs, Slides, and Images-People and Events (7 of 9)
    - 24.8 Photographs, Slides, and Images-People and Events (8 of 9)
  - Box 25
    - 25.1 Ripon Historic School Photographs
    - 25.2 Ripon Maps
    - 25.3 Ripon Research
    - 25.4 Schools-SUSD 150th Anniversary (2 of 2)
    - 25.5 Stockton and Copperopolis Railroad Right of Way
    - 25.6 Stockton Beautiful Publicity
    - 25.7 Stockton Civic Memorial Auditorium-Construction
    - 25.8 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Fundraising Lists, 1999
    - 25.9 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Maps, 1850-2000
    - 25.10 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1995 (7 of 7)
    - 25.11 Weber Point Events Center Publicity
    - 25.12 Woodbridge Masonic Lodge History
- Series VI: Rolled Oversize Maps, Plans, and Drawing, 1907-2004
  Includes maps, building plans, and drawings.
  - Box 26
    - Armory Plans, 1916
    - Clowes Residence, Alteration Plans, 1939
    - Henery Apartments Plans
    - Hotel Stockton, Rehabilitation Plans, 2002
    - Lockeford School, Renovation Plans, 2003
    - Ripon Map, 1920
    - Ripon Maps, 1920
    - Ripon Maps, 1907, 1920, 1925, 1951
    - Ripon Map, 1927
    - Stockton City Hall, Plans, 1923
    - Stockton City Hall, Roof Replacement Plans, 2004
    - Stockton State Hospital, Doctors Residence Plans, 1940, 1976
    - Stockton State Hospital, Superintendents Residence, Dining Room Plans, 1915
    - 428 E. Poplar, Remodel Plans, 2000
    - 640 N. San Joaquin Street, Fire Escape Plans, 2001
    - Pencil Drawing of Leslie Crow, no date